PALUDGNACH MATTEO

Full-Stack Software developer

SKILLS

FRONTEND

sveltekit - tailwind - flutter

BACKEND

typescript - golang

DEVOPS

github actions - argocd - kubernetes

DATABASES

postgres - redis - mongodb

CONTACTS

- **1** +39 3518853376
- ☑ paludgnachmatteo.dev@gmail.com
- portfolio.mp281x.xyz
- U Via Del Tei 18, Moimacco (UD)

LANGUAGES

ITALIAN - native

ENGLISH - fluent

SUMMARY

For several years I have been deeply passionate about web, application and API development by utilizing technologies such as Typescript, SvelteKit, Flutter, Golang, Postgres, Redis and MongoDB.

Additionally I have an interest in the DevOps, employing technologies like Docker and Kubernetes, UI/UX design and project planning.

I am continually seeking new challenges and i like to learn new programming languages to solve any problem presented to me. My strong organizational skills make me punctual and reliable in managing the projects entrusted to me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

NORDEST SERVIZI (stage) 17/01/2022 - 29/01/2022

System Engineer Tavagnacco (IT)

BIZAWAY (stage) 11/06/2023 - 04/06/2023 Backend Developer Spilimbergo (IT)

EDUCATION

ISIS A. Malignani 2017 - 2022 Final vote: 68 EQF: 4

Diploma in Infomatica e Telecomunicazioni

ITS Alto Adriatico 2022 - 2024

Final vote: -- EQF: 5

Tecnico Superiore Cloud Developer